Finding Aid for the Paul D. Boyer Papers, 1943-2009 LSC.2156
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Academia, 1941-2008; 1960-1993
  - Subseries 1.5: UCLA, 1974-2009; 1977-1990
    - UCLA Institutes: UCTDF/UCTDC Biotechnology commercialization (1 of 2)., 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Contains a retrospective note from Boyer about his opposition to a proposal by UC Vice President Ronald W. Brady for the establishment of UC-affiliated technology transfer companies. The plan called for the establishment of the non-profit UC Technology Development Foundation (UCTDF) and the for-profit UC Technology Development Company, the latter with the stated intention of bolstering funds for biotechnology research. The proposal was met with heavy resistance from a number of faculty who were concerned that the plan would undermine the ethos of scientific progress and was ultimately turned down.
    - UCLA Institutes: UCTDF/UCTDC Biotechnology commercialization (2 of 2)., 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Institutes: Relationships with DOE laboratories Los Alamos and Lawrence Livermore., 1981-1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - UCLA Institutes: Chancellor's Competitiveness Council., 2004-2007 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1943-2009; 1960-2000
  This series contains Boyer's general and research correspondence, which is virtually all professional in subject matter. Of major interest is correspondence delineating Boyer's research journey from his discoveries at the University of Minnesota, where he first began researching oxidative phosphorylation, to his eventual breakthrough on the binding change mechanism and rotational catalysis at UCLA in the 1970s. Correspondents Henry Lardy, David Green, Richard Cross, Nobelist Peter Mitchell, Richard Cross, Britton Chance, Efraim Racker, Kathryn LaNoue, and James Peter figure prominently in this series. For drafts with accompanying correspondence about specific articles, also see series 1.
  This series keeps the distinction between "correspondence" and "research correspondence" from Boyer's original filing system; however, researchers should note that there are not tangible thematic differences between "research correspondence" and general "correspondence," as virtually all is research-related. Frequent correspondents with Boyer have their own folders titled under their name and are arranged alphabetically. Less frequent correspondents were filed under "miscellaneous authors" and categorized by year. Series of correspondence concerning particular topics were kept in their original arrangement and filed under "miscellaneous authors".
  - Correspondence: Alberty, Robert., 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Allchin, Douglas., 1999-2002 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Atkinson, Dan (pH research)., 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Benson, Ellis., 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Chance, Britton., 1960-1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Choate, Glenda., 1973-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Cleland, William (Exchange Kinetics material)., 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: de Meis, Leopoldo regarding Boyer's one month stay in Rio de Janeiro & other parts of South America for interchage of scientific info., 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Du, Zi-Yun., 1986-1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Ernster, Lars., 1974-1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Feldman, Rick., 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Futai, Masamitsu., 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Graber, Peter., 1989-1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Gresser, Michael., 1973-2006 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Guerrero, Karen., 1985-1993 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Hackney, David (1 of 2)., 1973-2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Hackney, David (2 of 2)., 1973-2006 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Hammes, Gordon., 1982 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Contains a reflective note from Boyer about Hammes' opposition to Boyer's alternative site mechanism for ATP synthase.
  - Correspondence: Hutton, Lee., 1976-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Kandpal, Rajendra (1 of 2)., 1982-2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Kandpal, Rajendra (2 of 2)., 1982-2008 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Kasho, Vladimir., 1980-2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Katchalski, Ephraim., 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Kayalar, Celik (1 of 2)., 1973-1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Kayalar, Celik (2 of 2)., 1973-1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Kirkwood, Sam., 1955-1956, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: LaNoue, Kathryn., 1985-1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Lardy, Henry (1 of 2)., 1945-1995 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Lardy, Henry (2 of 2)., 1995-2000 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Lumry, Rufus., 1958-1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Lumry-Repke exchange, 1999., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: McIntire, Floyd., 1951-1959 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Melese, Teri., 1982-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Milgrom, Yakov., 1987-1994 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Murataliev, Marat., 1990-2003 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Ochoa, Severo., 1958-1963 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Penefsky, Harvey ([18]O Pi Data)., 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Peter, James., 1960-1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Phillips, Paul., 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Racker-Mitchell Group., 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Racker-Mitchell Group., 1975 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Rosen, Gary., 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Rosing, Jan., 1973-1998 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Scargill, MH regarding U of Victoria's proposal for a PhD program., 1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Senior, Alan., 1991-2005 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Shafer, Gunter., 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Shavit, Noun., 1980-1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Smith, Daniel., 1976-2002 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Smith, Linda Tombras., 1980-1994 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Stroop, Steve., 1982-1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: University of Minnesota Campus facilities, staff memos., 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: US Navy and War Manpower Commission., 1944-1946 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Vinkler, Channa., 1974-2003 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Viswanatha, T. (Nate)., 1955-1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Wada, Shohachi., 1963-1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Wise, John., 1984-2002 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Wood, Janet., 1984-1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Wu, Dan., 1983 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Xue, Zhi-Xiong., 1983-2000 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Zhou, Jun-Mei., 1948-2003 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, Kinetics Mechanism Derivation Discussions., 1960-1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, Naval correspondence (1 of 2)., 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, Naval correspondence (2 of 2)., 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, regarding Alan Senior's review of Boyer's work., 2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, regarding Myosin & ATP binding kinetics., 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, regarding Caspar Weinberger's LA Times letter to the Editor on Biomedical Research Funding., 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, regarding John Walker's 1994 Nature article. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, regarding William Allison's research., 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1940s., 1940-1949 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1950s (1 of 4)., 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1950s (2 of 4)., 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1950s (3 of 4)., 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1950s (4 of 4)., 1950-1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1960s (1 of 3)., 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1960s (2 of 3)., 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1960s (3 of 3)., 1960-1969 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1970s., 1970-1979 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 1990s., 1990-1999 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 2000s (1 of 2)., 2000-2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: misc. authors, 2000s (2 of 2)., 2000-2009 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Research Correspondence: Allison, Will., 1987-2000 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Research Correspondence: Beinert, Helmut., 1954-1958 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Research Correspondence: Berman, Mervyn., 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Research Correspondence: Butler, Larry., 1973-1979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Research Correspondence: Cross, Richard., 1969-1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Research Correspondence: Cross, Richard., 1973-1984 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Research Correspondence: Cross, Richard., 1985-2007 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Research Correspondence: Dahms, Steven., 1975-1985 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Research Correspondence: de Meis, Leopoldo., 1978-1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Research Correspondence: Fillingame, Robert., 1980-1997 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Research Correspondence: Futai, Masamitsu., 1986-1999 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Research Correspondence: Green, David., 1974-1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Research Correspondence: Hammes, Gordon., 1982 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Research Correspondence: Hatefi, Youssef., 1979-1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Research Correspondence: Hill, Terrell., 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Research Correspondence: Huennekens, Frank M., 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Research Correspondence: Jagendorf, Andre T., 1980-2000 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Research Correspondence: Kagawa, Yasuo., 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Research Correspondence: Kinosita, Kazuhiko., 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Research Correspondence: Kozlov, Igor A., 1981-1987 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Research Correspondence: Lehninger, Albert L., 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Research Correspondence: McCarty, Richard E., 1978-1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Research Correspondence: Malmstrom, Bo., 1960-1993 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Research Correspondence: Mal'yan, AN., 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Research Correspondence: Milgrom, Ya., 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Research Correspondence: Mitchell, Robert., 1977-1997 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Research Correspondence: Mitchell, Peter., 1961-1974 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Contains 2008 note from Boyer delineating the origins of some of the materials in this subseries, particularly for letters dating from the 1960s to 1980s with Peter Mitchell. Note explains that the original copies had been borrowed by Bruce Weber, who sent back the scans he made of the originals in 2006 at Boyer's request. However, during the processing period, many originals were found anyways despite claims of having "mysteriously disappeared", and a significant portion of these scans were removed from the collection.
  - Research Correspondence: Mitchell, Peter., 1984-1990 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Research Correspondence: Nishimura & Hersh on succinyl CoA synthetase., 1984 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Research Correspondence: Oster, George., 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Research Correspondence: Pederson, Peter L., 1974-1997 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Research Correspondence: Racker, Efraim., 1959-1977 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Research Correspondence: Repke, Kurt R. H., 1974-1994 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Research Correspondence: Rose, Irwin A., 1976-1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Research Correspondence: Senior, Alan E., 1977-1997 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Research Correspondence: Shavit, Noun., 1975-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Research Correspondence: Slater, EC (Bill)., 1973-1997 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Research Correspondence: Skulachev, Vladimir P., 1978-1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Research Correspondence: Vinogradav, Andrei D., 1984-2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Research Correspondence: Walker, John., 1985-1998 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Research Correspondence: Walker, John's Nobel lecture and biographical sketch., 1998 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Research Correspondence: Weber, Bruce., 1972-2006 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Research Correspondence: Yoshida, Masasuke., 1988-2001 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1970-1974. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1975-1979 (1 of 2). (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1975-1979 (2 of 2). (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1980. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1981. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1982. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1983. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1984. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1985-1989 (1 of 2). (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1985-1989 (2 of 2). (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1990-1994. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Research Correspondence: misc. authors, 1995-1999. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series 3: Awards & Donations, 1951-2009; 1980-2005
  This series contains material related to awards (including competitive funding from non-academic private institutions like the Guggenheim Foundation, and lectureships that function as awards like the Weizmann Lecture Series), and donations. Of particular interest are lectures, interviews, and correspondence relating to Boyer's 1997 Nobel Prize in Chemistry (also see series 2), as well as material relating to Boyer's 1955 Guggenheim Fellowship, 1989 Rose Award, and 1998 Seaborg Medal. The series also contains material documenting his nominating of other scholars for these awards. In addition, it contains material relating to Boyer's donating of his Nobel Prize monies to create the Boyer Postdoctoral Fellowships at UCLA, University of Minnesota, and the University of Wisconsin, as well as material relating to the creation of the Paul Boyer Endowed Chair at UCLA and the naming of Boyer Hall on UCLA's campus in large part through contributions by James Peter (a former postdoc of Boyer's) and the Albert Parvin Foundation. For other UCLA-related material, see series 1 and 2.
  Materials pertaining to "Awards" and "Nominations" are arranged in alphabetical order by name of the award. "Donations" and "Honorary Events" are sorted chronologically.
  CONTAINS RESTRICTED MATERIAL: Contains restricted nominee information.
  - Awards: The American Association for the Advancement of Science., 1951 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Awards: American Academy of Achievement Salute to Excellence Program., 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Awards: Canadian Biochemical Society National Lectureship., 1978-1980 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Awards: Guggenheim Fellowship, Sweden 1955., 1954-1961 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Awards: Lalor Foundation Fellowship, Woods Hole Marine Biological Laboratory., 1952 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Awards: National Academy of Sciences elected membership., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Awards: NIH Research Career Award Program., 1961 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize Ceremony Schedule., 1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Awards: Nobel Biographical Sketch., 1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Awards: Nobel blackboards., 2004 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Letters regarding the launch of an exhibition about Nobel Prize winners at the Mendenhall Sobieski Gallery in Pasadena, California.
  - Awards: Nobel Prize Commitments and Publications., 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Contains a copy of faxed draft of an essay written by Richard Wolkomir regarding Boyer and his team's work on ATP synthase for the 1997 edition of The Nobel Annual along with Boyer's edits.
  - Awards: Nobel Prize Correspondence (1 of 2)., 1997-2003 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize Correspondence (2 of 2)., 1997-2003 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize Interview with Istvan Hargittai., 1999 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize, misc. correspondence and press., 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize money settlements and funds., 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize related press., 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Awards: Nobel Prize related press., 1998-2002 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Awards: Paul-Lewis Award, ACS 1955 (lecture). (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Awards: Paul-Lewis Award, ACS 1955 (award information and correspondence)., 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Awards: Richard C. Tolman Medal, 1981., 1982 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Awards: Rose Award, Boyer 1989., 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Awards: UCLA Alumni Association Award., 1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Awards: 1998 UCLA Seaborg Award Symposium., 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Awards: Seaborg Medal Award, 2001 (honoring James Peter). (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Awards: University of Stockholm Honorary Degree., 1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Awards: University of Wisconsin Honorary Degree., 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Donations: Boyer Postdoctoral Excellence Award, University of Wisconsin., 1997-2008 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Donations: Boyer Postdoctoral Recognition Fund, UCLA., 1998-2008 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Donations: Creation of UCLA Paul Boyer Endowed Chair and Naming of Boyer Hall., 1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Donations: Boyer-Peter Postdoctoral Research Award, University of Minnesota., 1998-2008 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Donations: James Peter gift to Boyer Endowed Chair., 2001-2008 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Donations: Possible Establishment of Boyer graduate award at BYU., 1980, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Donations: UCLA Eureka Fund., 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Events: A Nobel Experience, 2x2 slides (1 of 2)., 1998 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Events: A Nobel Experience, 2x2 slides (2 of 2)., 1998 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Events: A Nobel Experience, 1998. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Events: UCLA Scholarship Dinner, Nov. 19 1998. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Lectures: Emeriti Association., 1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Lectures: Federation Proceedings, Rose Award Lecture., 1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Lectures: Nobel Lecture at UCLA "Energy, Life, and ATP" (1 of 2)., 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Lectures: Nobel Lecture at UCLA "Energy, Life, and ATP" (2 of 2)., 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lectures: UCLA Faculty Research Lecture, "How Living Cells Use Energy"., 1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lectures: Weizmann Memorial Lecture Series, 1984., 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Nominations: publications and CVs., 1986-2005 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Nominations: Albert Lasker Medical Research Award., 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Nominations: membership to American Philosophical Society., 2002 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Nominations: 1995 California Scientist of the Year Award. (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Nominations: Fellow of National Academy of Arts & Sciences., 1987 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Nominations: 2006 Harvey Prize Award., 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Nominations: 2006 National Academy of Sciences Award., 1991-2005 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Nominations: 2006 Nobel Prize., 2005 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Nominations: 1992 Repligen Award., 1991 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Nominations: 1995 Stein and Moore Award., 1994 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Nominations: 2001, 2004 Welch Foundation Award. (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Nominations: Wolf Foundation Prize., 1999 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Nominations: 2009 William C. Rose Award., 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Nominations: 1999 Nobel Prize. (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Nominations: 1988, 1991 Rose Awards., 1988, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Series 4: Government Funding and Contracts, 1955-1995
  This series contains material related to Boyer's government funding research grants, including those from the Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), Department of Energy (DOE), Energy Research and Development Administration (ERDA), National Science Foundation (NSF), and the United States Public Health Service (USPHS).
  Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically, first by government organization (AEC, DOE, etc.), and then chronologically based on the requested grant period. The sponsored project titles are included in the labels of some of the folder; those without are a renewal of the previous project grant.
  - Grants: AEC Progress Reports, 1963-1970, "Isotopic Studies on Structure-Function Relationships of Nucleic Acids and Enzymes". (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1966-1967. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1967-1968. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1968-1969. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for extension from June 1, 1969 - July 31, 1969. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1969-1970. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1970-1971., 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Grants: AEC Progress Reports, 1970-1975. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1971-1972. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1972-1973. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1973-1974. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Grants: AEC Renewal Request for 1974-1975. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Grants: DOE Progress Report for 1975-1978, "Energy Capture & Use in Plants and Bacteria". (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1979., 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1980., 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1981., 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1982-1984., 1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1982-1984., 1981-1984 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Grants: DOE, Foreign Travel Funding for 1982-1984. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1984., 1983-1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1985. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1985-1987., 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1986., 1985 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1987., 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1988., 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1988-1990 (1 of 2)., 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1988-1990 (2 of 2)., 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1989., 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1990., 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1990-1992., 1990-1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)